<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>McKinley Park Development Council</title>
    <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on McKinley Park Development Council</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Home Buyer and Landlord Seminar</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/homelandlordseminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/homelandlordseminar/</guid>
      <description>Join Mark S. Javier from the McKinley Park Development Council for a New Home Buyer &amp;amp; Landlord Seminar, 7 p.m. to 8:30 p.m. on Thursday, May 24, 2018, at Bethany Baptist Church, 3532 S. Hoyne Ave., Chicago.
This information session and mediated discussion will focus on the issues pertinent to purchasing a home and operating as a successful and responsible landlord. Attend to connect with experts in the local real estate market and learn best practices for home ownership and managing tenants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Kids - Lets Paint a Mural in the Park!</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/parkmural/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/parkmural/</guid>
      <description>Calling all McKinley Park parents and children! Help the McKinley Park Development Council and the McKinley Park Advisory Council transform the abandoned playground bathroom building from graffiti magnet into a mural designed and painted by our children! Submit drawings on the sheet below by May 15 to mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil@gmail.com  - or turn in at the Park Fieldhouse or Library. McKinley Park resident and artist Victoria Rodriguez will select and convert our children&amp;rsquo;s drawings into a mural that highlights the things we love about our neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May Meeting! May 16, 2018</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingmay2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingmay2018/</guid>
      <description>Join us for our monthly public meeting at the McKinley Park Fieldhouse, for some neighborhood updates and reports from the various MPDC sub committees. Wednesday, April 16, 2018 7pm - 8:30pm. 
McKinley Park Fieldhouse - Brown Room  2210 W Pershing Road, Chicago, IL
Special thanks to our host, The Chicago Park District  We hope you can join us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April Meeting! April 18, 2018</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingapril2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingapril2018/</guid>
      <description>Join us for our monthly public meeting at Aquinas Literacy Center, for some neighborhood updates and reports from the various MPDC sub committees. Wednesday, April 18, 2018 7pm - 8:30pm.
Aquinas Literacy Center 1751 W 35th St, Chicago, IL
Special thanks to our host, Aquinas Literacy Center!  We hope you can join us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Rivers Project Walk Audit</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/walkaudit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/walkaudit/</guid>
      <description>Calling all McKinley Parkers! Did you know the Chicago River forms the eastern border of McKinley Park? Help us improve - and improve access to! - this neighborhood treasure (well&amp;hellip;it will be!).  Join the McKinley Park Development Council on Saturday April 7  from 9-11 am at the Eleanor Boathouse (2828 S Eleanor)  and learn what a Walk Audit is - and how to do one - with the goal of ensuring that McKinley Park&amp;rsquo;s voices are heard as we work to improve access to the River from McKinley Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Social Meeting! March 21, 2018</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingmar2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingmar2018/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a tour of Razzmatazz Family Fun Center, some brief neighborhood updates and then a lot of family friendly fun. Wednesday, March 21, 2018 7pm - 8:30pm.
Razzmatazz Family Fun Center 3900 S. Ashland Ave., Chicago, IL 60609 (773) 376-2900
Special thanks to our host, Razzmatazz Family Fun Center!  We hope you can join us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPDC Gets a Shout Out from Cook County Board Candidate</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/alma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/alma/</guid>
      <description>Candidate for Cook County Board of Commissioners, Alma Anaya posted an editorial, What is the Future of Our Neighborhood? in the McKinleyPark.news, citing the work of the MPDC in the context of development in McKinley Park. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Public Meeting! Jan 17, 2018</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingjan2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/meetingjan2018/</guid>
      <description>Join us at our first public meeting at the National Latino Education Institute Wednesday, January 17, 2018 7pm - 8:30pm.
Learn about what we&amp;rsquo;ve been doing, what we plan to do and how you can get involved to help make McKinley Park an even better neighborhood.
Special thanks to our host, National Latino Education Institute!  We hope you can join us!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Meet &amp; Greet at One City Tap Dec 18, 2017</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/onecityjan2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/onecityjan2018/</guid>
      <description>Please join us on Monday December 18, 2017 6:30 - 8 pm at One City Tap (3115 S Archer)
We have lots of reasons to celebrate: The holiday season, our founding year, the grant we recently received from Chicago Metropolitan Agency for Planning (CMAP) to create a Neighborhood Plan for McKinley Park, and you, our excellent neighbors!
We look forward to a 2018 full of McKinley Park Activity: We are opening up our membership to the entire community, starting with our first meeting January 17 (mark your calendars!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizens Guide to Zoning Workshop Video</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/zoning_wkshop_vid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/zoning_wkshop_vid/</guid>
      <description>Video of the Citizens Guide to Zoning Workshop held on October 16, 2017.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen&#39;s Guide to Zoning: Understand How Development Works in Your Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/save-the-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/save-the-date/</guid>
      <description>With vacant lots, demolitions, and rezoning applications pointing to new development coming to McKinley Park, the McKinley Park Development Council (MPDC) invites you and your neighbors to attend our inaugural workshop - a Citizens Guide to Zoning: Understanding how development works in your neighborhood.
Join MPDC and your neighbors to learn and ask questions about what zoning is; how it works; and what it means for our neighborhood, so we can move forward, together, with more knowledge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Need a Plan</title>
      <link>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/why-we-need-a-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mckinleyparkdevelopmentcouncil.org/news/why-we-need-a-plan/</guid>
      <description>In this video we explain why we think McKinley Park needs a plan. The video helped us win a grant from the Chicago Community Trust.   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>